Yes, of course, there is
Да нету тут конечно
no communication here, how and how do you
никакой коммуникации как а как вы на
go to the bucket or
ведро ходите или
why? Well, the toilet, well, that is, well, as
что почему Ну туалет ну то есть ну как
there is, uh, a
есть
toilet, Well, yes, there is one on the other side of the yard,
туалет Ну да в другой стороне двора есть
that is, if at night, for example, at 3 am you
то есть если ночью например в 3 ночи вам
get hot, you should
припекло вы должны
get dressed exactly Yes Ino Well  Of course it’s
одеться именно Да Ино Ну конечно
natural, but it’s good And if in the
естественно а хорошо А если в
stove Why in the stove, then he went out into
печку Почему в печку то он вышел в
the garden and
огород и
that’s all, there was such a cool guy
всё только что парень такой прикольный
with an
был с
accordion in Ukrainian, I wanted to
гармошкой на Украинско мне хотел да
drink something something in
спивать что-нибудь что-нибудь на
Ukrainian, I can also drink something, something, something can
украинском я тоже могу спивать что что
be done here Name it  some song
мо свать вот Назовите какую-то песню
to
которую вам
sing to you Let's go ocean something not
спеть Давай океан что-нибудь не что-то
something Russian folk there Katyusha Maybe
такое русское народное там Катюш Может
it's
там
not Katyusha Katyusha heard that I don't
не Катюшу Катюшу слышал что я тебе не
know you there early in the morning at dawn we went
знаю там рано утром на рассвете мы пошли
there to the neighbor's garden Moldavian
там в соседский сад молдаванку что-то
something our advice  Let's make a
такое наше совет Давайте Загадайте
wish from Moldovans but it's not Russian
загадать молдован но это не русская
Listen, okay, let's give some
Слушай ну хорошо давайте какую-то
Russian Soviet song of ours Yes, now
русскую советскую нашу песню Да сейчас
we'll
мы её
remake it Why remake it And I'm a master Well,
переделаем А зачем передел А я мастер Ну
I'll remake the music for modern Lakh,
я на современный Лах переделаю
no need to do it If it's good I'm in the
музыку делать не надо Если хорошо Я в
original in the original Come on, tell me
оригинале в оригинале Да ну скажите
what
какую
song Come on, you
песню Давай ты же меня
pissed me off in the wrong way in Russian, let’s make sure
пидманула не так по-русски давайте чтобы
you don’t understand in Ukrainian Why are you saying
вы же не поймёте по-украински Почему ты
what I’m saying? Well, I’m not saying it, it’s me I
что я вообще скую Ну не скую я я это я Я
understand everything in Ukrainian Where am
всё понимаю по укра Вы откуда
I from? Siberia Siberia
вообще я Сибирь Сибирь
And from a town or village
А из посёлка или села
some kind of not I’m from the city, it’s just that you have
какого-то не Я из города просто у вас
some kind of tulle, some kind of tulle,
какие-то ну эти тюли какие-то такие как
well, not city stuff Well, I’m at the dacha, but I
ну не городские Ну так я же на даче
understood everything at the dachas Like everything is at the
что-то а понял все на дачах Типа все на
dachas Well, no, I understand And you have a dacha  with
дачах Ну что нет понял А у вас дача с
gas heating or a
газовым отоплением или
stove, no, I have gas,
печным не ну у меня газ есть как бы да
no, it’s not like it’s connected, but I
не ну не то что он подведён А у меня
just have a cylinder. Well, is it just that you
просто ну баллон Ну это это просто вы
built a dacha for yourself, or you just bought it in the village,
себе построили дачу или это в селе
you bought a house in the village, a
просто купили в деревне купили дом да
long time ago  it was built back in Soviet times,
давным-давно её ещё в советское время
when I was not yet born. And when did you
построили Когда ещё я не родился А вы
buy it, when I was not yet born, when it was
купили когда я ещё не родился когда оно
good, when this dacha was transferred to you Well,
хорошо когда вам перешла эта дача Ну
damn, when did you transfer it, I don’t remember the
блин когда ты перешла я не помню тебе то
date that Well, this is still Soviet post, that’s not the
дату что Ну это ещ Советская пост не
point  that I am an architect myself
дело в том что я архитектор сам
Yes, I’m interested in how buildings were made in
Да мне интересно как постройки делали в
Siberia in Soviet times, you can show them how
Сибири в советское время можете показать
they were made, well Show the layouts
даза они делались ну Показать планировки
Which of what were from that And they didn’t do the
Какие из чего было с того И делали не
layouts around the stove like
как планировки там вокруг печи как
they did Well, that is, it’s interesting to me as an architect
делали Ну то есть мне как архитектору
Yes I have  18 years of practice
это интересно Да у меня 18 лет практики
in 2 years it will be
через 2 года будет
20 something I have in a second
20 что-то у меня подо секундочку
And I can’t hear you well say something
А я тебя плохо слышу говори что-нибудь
once and again I can hear it normally the connection is
раз-раз слышно нормально связь попадает
true no no no no
правда не не не не Переключайся не
Switch don’t switch don’t switch don’t
Переключайся не Переключайся не
switch Yes I want you to
Переключайся Да я хочу чтобы ты мне
show me  From a professional point of view, I’m
показал мне с профессиональной точки
interested in how headphones are used,
зрения Интересно как наушникам не
but now I can hear you, so yes,
то да вот сейчас тебя слышу так так да
show me how
то покажите как у вас
it’s
оно
set up I can hear me listening, I can
обустроено слышно меня слушаю
hear what
слышно что
it is Yes, now I can hear you well
такое Да вот сейчас слышу тебя хорошо
Show me Yes, I’m just interested in how the
Покажите Да мне интересно просто как
interior was formed there, how the relative
формировалось там интерьер как взаимное
arrangement of the rooms  in the Soviet Union
расположение комнат в Советском Союзе
it was done in Siberia I saw how it is here in
делалось в Сибири Я видел как у нас в
Ukraine I’m just writing a scientific paper
Украине Я как раз ээ научную работу пишу
about the architecture of the Soviet era, you’re
об архитектуре советского вре ты сес при
serious Yes, what kind
серьёзно Да какой я
of architect am I?
архитектор И что И что я тебе какую
household
что ли тоже да Ну как бытовая
architecture of the population in the Soviet
архитектура э населения в Советском
Union Well, you want to plunge straight into the Soviet Union
Союзе А ну хочешь прямо в Советский Союз
Well, look at this,
окунуться Ну вот смотри это прямо вообще
nothing has changed at all in the Soviet Union I’m
ничего не менялось Советского Союза Я
just such an ascetic, look like that, you
прямо прямо такой аскет такого смотри
see No, well, it doesn’t make sense
вот видишь Не ну так оно не имеет смысла
to change it if it’s a dacha Yes, it’s a stove like that
менять если это дача Да это печь так
it turns out that here is the room
получается вот здесь вот комната
damn it And look And on your stoves they made a
блин А смотрите А у вас на печах делали
place for a bed where you can lie
место для лежанки где там лежать можно
on the stove to bask like in
на печи греться как на
Russia Now I’ll show you for a second
Руси Сейчас секунду покажу тебе
now, well, for a second
ещё сейчас ну секунду
you can hear me and I can
слышишь меня да слышу
hear me perfectly, otherwise I only have one
слышу отлично а то у меня что-то один
earphone  it looks like he
наушник видать
died, what do you want to hear or
сдох что ты хочешь-то услышать или
see? I don’t know the layout, how do
увидеть Я не по Ну планировки как вот
you get out into the streets?
выход вас выход на улиц делается веран
There is a veranda, yes, that is, the veranda
есть веранда да то есть веранда
of the classic you Drone here I hope you won’t
классика ты Дрон сюда Надеюсь не
launch it. How will I launch it?
запустишь А как я запущу
Who needs it? I understand
Кому оно нужно понял
and know everyone right now  in short, the
да зна сечас всех вот короче вот
crustacean understood the wreath
рачка понял венка
to the house, the entrance is a summer kitchen like that, but not
в дом вход это летняя кухня такая да не
A Pony, the entrance is here, yes, yes, here, as
А Поня вход вот здесь вот да да здесь
I understand it, it turns out that the rooms are
вот я так понял получается комнаты
around the stove Yes, so that it heats all the
вокруг печи Да чтобы она обогрева все
rooms, yes, this is the logic, well, yes,
комнаты да вот это логика такая ну да
this is what material the house is made of
это а дом из какого
well, how can I tell you? Well, it’s
ну как как тебе сказать
lined with a joint venture, and in the
обшита СП а
middle this one is like
середине этот как
timber, timber, that is, a wooden house,
он брус брус то есть деревянный дом да
yes, yes, of course, and the stove is Clay, well,
ну да ну конечно а печь Глиняная так Ну
yes, I understand, well, it’s like it’s Brick, but it’s
да понял Ну она как она Кирпичная но она
lined with clay anyway, I understand. Yes,
глинная обложена всё равно понял Да а
how did the communications work now?  I
как вот сейчас коммуникации провели я
understand in the Soviet Union there was no
понимаю в Советском Союзе не было
communication sewerage water supply has
коммуникации канализации водопровод
now been installed here Yes, of course there is
сейчас провели тут Да нету тут конечно
no communication here How do you go to the bucket
никакой коммуникации Как как вы на ведро
and
ходите и
what why Well, the toilet, well, that is, well, how is there a
что почему Ну туалет ну то есть ну как
toilet Well, yes, on the other side of the yard there is, that
туалет Ну да в другой стороне двора есть
is, if at night for example in  3 nights you are
то есть если ночью например в 3 ночи вам
hot, you should
припекло вы должны
get dressed, yes Well, of course it’s
одеться именно да Ну конечно естественно
good And
хорошо А
if there’s
если
a stove Yes, why did he go out into
печку Да почему в печку он вышел в
the garden into the stove? That’s it. I understand. That is, you don’t even have to
огород всё Поня То есть даже не надо
go to the toilet.
идти до туалета
I have a garden, but of
У меня же огород да
course I don’t. Yes, if only for the sake of this,
конечно ме Да если только ради это ещ
everyone can still go there  if at night
можно туда каждый раз ну ночью
you'll go damn sure you'll go crazy Well yes So
блин конечно с ума сойдёшь Ну да Так
damn By the time you get there
блин Пока дойдёшь
of course Well yes My
конечно Ну да У моей
grandmother isn't like she has her own
бабушки не как бы это у неё есть своё
bucket I
ведро
mean where does she live in the city does she live with her
скаже в смысле где живёт в городе жит у
grandmother in the city
бабушки в городе
a bucket why does she live in the city I say Oh
ведро почему она в городе говорю живёт А
well  she comes to the dacha all the time early And I
ну она же приезжает на дачу всё рано А
understand everything, she has her own cucumbers here,
всё понял у неё здесь есть огурчики сво
otherwise this is your grandmother’s dacha and not yours, I
а то это дача вашей бабушки а не ваша
forgot something Why is my grandmother
что-то забыл Почему моя а что бабушка
coming to your dacha? Well, because
приезжает к вам на дачу Ну потому что
it’s my grandmother, I love her and she
это моя бабушка я её люблю и она
comes to your dacha to make
приезжает к вам на дачу сделать
cucumbers Well, yes, she doesn’t have any
огурчики Ну да у не есть
garden beds here. Let her understand everything, that is, you allocated an area for grandma so that she wouldn’t single out anything there. She wanted it here. That is, I have it here as my own deckchair. I have
тут как свой шезлонг У меня есть тут
my own swing here.  I have my own territory
своя качеля У меня есть своя территория
I told her Grandma, please
Я ей сказал Бабушка вот сюда пожалуйста
don’t come here, but do whatever you want there, I
не заходи А вот там что хочешь творяй
understand Well, I understand, yes. That is, in
вообще понял Ну понял да То есть в
principle, they are just
принципе им пенсионерам им как раз
interested in the ridge there, but wait, and
интересно там на гряд а подождите А
now somewhere Grandma’s bucket is here in the
сейчас гдето Бабушкино ведро оно тут в
house Well  why the hell does she know? She probably
доме Ну почему блин знает Наверно она
snatched it from me somewhere, I don’t know where.
его от меня шкет куда-то я не знаю где
No, wait, stop, wait, stop. What are
Не ну подожди стоп подожди стоп ПП что
those grandmothers in the bucket interested in? Wait, I
те бабушки на ведро интересует Подожди я
don’t understand. Let’s do this. That is, you don’t know
не понял Давай так То есть ты не знаешь
which bucket the grandmother goes to; she left; I
в какое ведро ходит бабушка она уехала
know. No, I  I saw I saw that it
знаю Нет я видел я видел что оно оно
is it is this bucket but it’s not exactly a bucket
есть это ведро но оно именно не ведро
it’s just like a toilet you know how a
оно именно вот как туалет знаешь как
toilet is sold here you know
туалет у нас продаётся вот такое знаешь
like a bucket Bele I don’t know that You can
как ведро Беле я такое не знаю Можешь
show it to me Well what am I telling you Now
показать это бе Ну я тебе что Сейчас
I’ll look for grandmothers for a bucket what
буду искать бабушки на ведро что ли Да
Yes, how white it is, toilet, I’m wondering
ну как оно бело туалет мне ж интересно
how it is, yes, we communicate normally, well,
как это да же нормально общаемся ну
interesting, well, because I thought it was
интересно ну потому что я думал что это
just, I can’t tell you, I, Well, I, I
просто я тебе не могу сказать я Я Ну я я
can’t, Well, type it on the Internet. I thought
не могу Ну набери в интернете Я думал
it was an ordinary cylindrical bucket and
это обычное ведро цилиндрической формы и
there they are shorter and then they take it out no no
туда они короче и потом выносят нет нет
olet and go to the toilet
олет а ходят в туалет
I don’t know Well listen well I don’t know
Я не знаю Ну слушай ну я тебе не мо
for the first time I heard this that the bucket is white The
впервые такое слышал что ведро бело
toilet is like some kind of chickpeas you say
Туалет это как нуту какую-то говоришь
anyway well how is this a bucket a bucket biyo I’m
вообще ну как это ведро ведро биё мне
interested Look at the point  what, how is
интересно Смотрите дело в том что ну как
it, I want to understand how it turns out Well,
это я хочу понять как получается Ну это
they are pensioners, if they go to the bucket,
ж пенсионеры они если ходят на ведро
then she needs to take it out in the morning,
потом ей надо это утром вынести как это
how is this bucket worth?
ведро стоит Какой ты пошлый фу Какой ты
grandmothers live, well wait, what do you have, what do you have
бабушки ну подожди а у вас что у вас что
in all the villages there are just
во всех деревнях есть именно прямо
toilets just right sewerage Yes,
туалеты именно прямо канализация Да
right in all the villages they do yes they
прямо во всех деревнях делают да э
make a well septic tank like I really do
делают колодец септик типа реально делаю
Yes you can now now find those who are
Да ты сейчас сейчас найти э тех кто
shorter with a wooden toilet Yes on the street
короче с деревянным туалетом Да на улице
it’s
это
just a rarity in the USA Well, you have
редкость просто США Ну у вас же есть
dachas, you do have a dacha and
дачи дача же есть и
it’s not at home it’s not at home don’t confuse it’s not at
это не дома это не дома не путай это не
home where we live we don’t live there we do
дома где мы живём мы там не живём мы
n’t live here how long do you stay in
здесь не живём сколько вы пребываете в
this dacha How long
этой даче Сколько в этой даче
do you stay in this dacha exactly what  I need how much
пребываете тебе именно что надо сколько
I arrive when I come to some
прибывают я когда приезжаю в какую-то
recreation center for the weekend Yes, I don’t go
базу отдыха на выходные Да я же не хожу
there either to a wooden
туда тоже в деревянный
toilet, now everywhere in short, the toilets are
туалет сечас всюду короче туалеты
normal here, not a recreation center. Listen,
нормальные здесь не база отдыха Слушай у
at all of our recreation centers,
нас на всех базах отдыха само собой
of course, everything here is well-equipped, there
здесь конечно благоустроено всё здесь
are no wooden ones  there are no toilets there Of course there is no
нету деревянных там туалетов Конечно нет
such thing. What kind of toilet do you have here?
такого А какой у вас туалет здесь
It’s just that I have a wooden toilet specifically at my dacha.
просто здесь у меня конкретно на дачи
You don’t
деревянный туалет Ты что не не не
don’t don’t understand or that yes I mean. Well, what I’m
разумеешь или что да разумею Ну то что я
saying is that an old grandmother should
говорю и бабушка старенькая должна
go to the bucket and then
ходить на ведро а потом ведро это
pull the bucket. Listen, what if  where to pull Well,
тянуть Слушай а если куда тянуть Ну
pull into this one, where does she throw it in
тянуть в этот она ж куда выкидывает в
that toilet Then in the morning I Why the hell are you
тот туалет Потом утром я Ты что блин ты
asking me such intimate details,
такие интимные подробности мне задаёшь
well wait, where does she
ну подожди а куда она
throw it away, what the hell are you doing? Why do you
выкидывает фу какой ты пош Зачем тебе
need this at all? Wait, I just don’t
это надо вообще бра Подожди Я просто не
understand how this happens.  you from the point of
понимаю как это происходит у вас с точки
view of hygiene Maybe it’s like from this that
зрения гигиены Может это типа из этого
a lot of diseases creep in there.
куча болезней там
Who. We people have a lot of diseases there,
лезет У кого У нас у людей да у вас там
no, we don’t have a lot of diseases, but where do these
не у нас куча болезней не но Куда эти
go then she throws them out in the beds
деваются потом она их грядки выкидывает
or in the
или в
toilet Listen, damn this story
туалет Слушай ну блин эта история
is probably silent  And if
умалчивает наверное хорошо А если у
grandma has a problem? Well, if grandma has a
бабушки покра Хорошо если у бабушки там
problem with her stomach and she
солу с желудком проблеме и она за ночь
goes three or four times a night, it ends up in the
три-четыре раза ходит она получается в
same bucket,
одно и то же самое ведро
then you told me yourself. You
на вать то ты сам рассказал Ты же сам
told me about grandma. I didn’t even know
Рассказал мне про бабушку я даже не знал
that.  you have a grandmother, you can
что у тебя есть бабушка може
talk, yes they spoke normally, but
разговаривать да нормально говорили но
you said that you have a
ты же типа сказал что у тебя есть
grandmother and she walks on a bucket. It wasn’t my
бабушка и она ходит на ведро Это не я
idea. Well, I already told you.
придумал Ну так я тебе уже сказал Да ну
Yes, there is
такое есть Что Ну да есть у нас у нас
such a thing.  toilet and what do
есть вот вот такой туалет и что тут
we have here, you know the city We
такого у нас есть понимаешь город У нас
have an apartment Well, that is, where we live
есть квартира Ну то есть где мы живём
permanently and there is just a dacha where we
постоянно а есть просто дача где мы
get high at Well, like in the village, why
кайфуем при Ну как в деревне жим Почему
don’t you do it? Why don’t you, out of
вы например не сделаете Почему вы из
concern for your grandmother, make a
заботы для бабушки не сделайте
normal toilet here?  Well, so that grandma
нормальный унитаз тут ну чтобы бабушка в
can go to normal conditions because it’s
нормальные условия ходила потому что
a mockery of grandma, that she
издевательство над бабушкой что она
should sit on a bucket damn 70
должна на ведро садиться блин 70 с
something years old Babush How old is grandma you are,
чем-то лет Бабуш Сколько бабушке лет ты
that’s the same thing to you, what difference does it make to you how
это самое Тебе какая разница сколько там
old grandma is? Well, how old grandma are you
лет бабушки Ну сколько бабушки лет ты
now, what are you talking about now?  that I
сейчас ты сейчас о чём говоришь что я
should make a septic tank or something Personally Well,
должен септик сделать что ли Лично Ну
yes I mean Well, yes What is the problem with a
да В смысле Ну да А в чём проблема зде
septic tank And what is the problem with not making a
септик А в чём проблема сделать не
septic tank And why do this, so that the
септик А для чего это делать ну чтоб
grandmother does not suffer
бабушка не мучилась
if if this dacha is it, in principle
если если эта дача она она в принципе
it can be temporary it  maybe
она может быть временная она может быть
today, for example, yes, or maybe Well,
сегодня например есть да а может быть Ну
in 2 years I’ll sell it How much does it cost
через 2 года я её продам Сколько стоит
to make a
сделать
septic tank Well, I don’t know, I don’t know how much even
септик Ну не знаю я не знаю сколько даже
good stop and washbasin Do you have a
хорошо стоп а умывальник У вас есть
washbasin do you even have where the water
умывальник у вас вообще есть откуда вода
comes from water from the sea comes from Which
идёт вода из моря идёт Из какого
sea  from our sea in Novosibirsk
моря из нашего мор в Новосибирске из
from the sea What Novosibirsk are you from
моря Из какого Новосибирска ты взл вы из
Siberia somewhere From what sea Well yes A And
Сибири где-то Из какого моря Ну да А А
what does it have to do with Novosibirsk well from what
причём здесь с новосибирс ну с какого
sea does
моря
it come from a
идёт с
reservoir What kind of
водохранилища Что за
reservoir Well show that you have a
водохранилище Ну покажи что у вас есть
washbasin that you have hydrogen  yes, I don’t
умывальник что у вас водород есть я не
believe it because then there would be a septic tank
верю потому что тогда бы септик был
anyway, you have somewhere the water from the
полюбому у вас же куда-то вода с
washbasin must leak out, but what
умывальника должна утека а а что мне с
will it do for me if I show it?
этого будет если я покажу Не мне просто
just
так не будет может не покажет просто
curious If the water means it should be a
интересно Если вода значит должно
drain sewer And where it flows
водосток канализация А куда оно течёт
showed And or does it flow into a bucket I
показал А или оно в ведро течёт я тебе
showed you yes And where it flows The water flows I
показал да А куда течёт Вода стекает я
showed you I showed you the question Now it’s
показал я тебе показал вопрос Теперь у
not clear to me And where this Water flows
меня непонятно А куда эта Вода стекает
was shown Yes I see there is a faucet  and the question is
показали Да я вижу кран есть а вопрос
Where
Куда
ONT did I show you? We had what kind of
ОНТ я тебе показал у нас был какой
agreement what kind of agreement am I showing you and
договор какой договор я тебе показываю и
everything wasn’t everything wasn’t everything you
всё нет не было всё не было всё вы
just said that you would show it, that is, it’s
просто сказали что покажете да то есть
just not clear to me Explain the system
просто мне непонятно Объясните систему
where the water flows Do you have Well, some
куда утекает вода У вас есть Ну какой-то
or  it flows into the bucket there and there is a pit
или оно в ведро течёт там да яма есть
So what is the problem there is a pit So
Так а в чём проблема яма есть Так а в
what is the problem with making a
чём проблема сделать
septic tank a septic tank is that there is no such
септик септик в том что здесь нету такой
area here to install a septic tank
площади чтобы септик ещ
and what area is
ставить а какую площадь
needed Well some area is needed for a
нужно Ну какую-то площадь нужно для
septic tank I
септика
understand Okay okay I’ll go  I understood the topic in short,
понял Ладно хорошо Пойду я понял короче
I was just wondering, as an
тему мне просто интересно было как
architect, what life was like. That is, it
архитектору как это вот быт То есть
turns out that people in the Soviet Union
получается люди у вас в Советском Союзе
lived there without
там жили без
toilets; this toilet on the street is now
унитазов этот туалет на улице впе сейчас
being practiced.
практикуется Троль такой тоже типа для
at least in the dachas It’s not,
ещё Ну по крайней мере на дачах Это не
it’s not private houses, of course in private
это не частные дома конечно в частных
houses there are septic tanks, that’s
домах там септики стоят это это
normal,
нормально
of course you don’t think that’s what it
конечно ты не думаешь что там именно вот
is in the cities. Yes, that’s exactly the
есть в городах Да там именно вот
buildings that are private houses, of
застройки которые именно частные дома
course there are septic tanks there, but here in the
там конечно септики стоят а здесь на
dachas Well, no  such
дачах Ну нет такой
a need and the World Cup, for example, at the World Cup, I understand
нужды а ЧМ например вот в ЧМ ме понимаю
what the trick is then to come to such a
в чём фишка тогда вот приехать на такую
dacha where there is no toilet and
дачу где нету унитаза и тут
hang out here. I mean, well, how do you just feel like
тусить В смысле Ну как себя просто как
in the village, neither in the city
как в деревне почувствовать ни в городе
nor in a box, how can I tell you how, how does
ни в коробке как тебе сказать как как
it make a difference?  Well, that is, or you live
это разница какая Ну то есть или ты
in an apartment, yes You live Well,
именно вот в квартире да Живёшь Ну вот
no Well, now you are sitting, for example, at
не Ну вот вы сейчас сидите например на
work in a store, for example, there,
работу на работу в магазин например там
I don’t know where else, to the beach, to
ну я не знаю ещё куда на пляж там
go somewhere, to go on
куда-то уехать там поехать
vacation, or you can always go to the
отдохнуть или ты можешь постоянно на
dacha  go there and take care of your beds
дачу ездить там своими грядками
Well, grandma
заниматься Ну грядками бабушка
is busy with the beds. What are you doing at the dacha? I’m just goofing about, that
занимается А вы чем на даче
’s all. I’m just goofing off. I have a boat. I’m going for a ride on the reservoir. That’s all. That is, you’re kind of
водохранилищу А всё То есть вы типа на
going out on a boat, I understand you’re here.
лодке катаетесь понял вы вы тут
Come for the night, it’s just possible
Приходите на ночь получается просто
to spend the night  Well, why not me, why am I
переночевать Ну почему не я почему я
doing everything here, as it were, well, I’m
здесь всё делаю как бы ну я здесь дрова
chopping wood there, well, I’m doing everything that needs to be served,
рублю там ну всё делаю что нужно подаче
well,
ну как как тебе сказать что такое свой
how can I tell you what your home is? If you don’t know what your home is. How
Если ты не знаешь что такое свой дом Как
can I tell you what my
я тебе могу рассказать что такое свой
home is here? Well  everything needs to be done anyway, in
дом здесь Ну всё надо делать всё равно в
any case, how everything should be done, but they
любом случае да как всё надо делать а
didn’t do a septic tank, this is what I can’t
септика не сделали вот это я не могу
understand Damn, sorry, please, I
понять Блин ну Простите пожалуйста вот
didn’t read before you that I didn’t
перед вами не читался что я септика не
do a septic tank, guess what, no one here has a
сделал прикинь здесь вообще ни у кого
septic tank,
септика
no, they’re all
Нет все
some kind of buckets  generally vulgar listen
вёдра какой-то вообще пошлый слушай
here no one has buckets
здесь никто не вёдра
here there is a toilet here that
здесь есть здесь есть именно туалет
everyone goes to the toilet only
который все ходят в туалет только
grandmothers
бабушки
buckets you don’t you understand or what
вёдра ты ты ты что не понимаешь или что
wait did you say everything turns out they
подожди ты сказал все то получается туда
go there Why doesn’t your grandmother go there Are
ходят А что твоя бабушка не ходит туда
you really like that I can  understand
Ты что такой в натуре могу понять
Look, everyone is walking, grandmothers are walking, what is your
Смотри все ходят бабушки ходят что твоя
ba If at night, wait for her If a woman
ба Если ночью подожди ей Если женщине
needs it at night, why should a woman go to the
надо ночью почему женщина должна идти в
toilet on the other on the other side of the
туалет на другой на другую сторону
site, it’s better for her to just go to this
участка ей лучше просто сходить в этот
septic tank And then this septic tank is about
септик А потом этот септик про
what septic tank Don’t you understand?
какой септик Ты что не понимаешь я тебе
what did he say What kind of septic tank is a septic tank -
только что сказал Какой септик септик -
this is exactly this bucket, it’s
это вот Вот именно вот это ведро
called a septic tank, it closes with
называется септик оно закрывается
a lid. And I understand everything, this is a special
крышкой А всё понял это специальная
design of a bucket with a lid, this is a septic tank, that
конструкция ведро с крышка это септик то
is, on a lid, and it doesn’t stink until the morning,
есть на крышко и оно до утра не воняет
well, damn it, Now I understand, I think it’s
ну ну блин Теперь я понял Я думаю это
without a lid  bucket What is it there it stinks
без крышки ведро Что там оно оно воняет
understood everything And these are new biora It’s just that before
понял всё А это новые биора Просто я до
this technology I didn’t know
этой технологии не знал
what you got it for,
на чего ты взял что
what it is, if of course a woman
она ну е если если конечно женщине
wants it there And if there is a great need, then of
хочется там А по большой нужде то
course she will go
конечно она уйдёт
there to that toilet in the main But
туда в то в тот туалет в основной Но
if she needs a little help, why should she go there,
если ей надо по малой зачем ей туда идти
she just goes to this septic tank And in the
она просто э сходит на этот септик А
morning, the flight out and that’s it, no problems, I
утром вылет вот и всё нет проблем
understand that’s all I understand, that is,
никаких это понял Всё то я понял то есть
this is a septic tank for liquid fractions
это септик для жидких фракций
Well, I guess I can’t with everything, give me
Ну наверно да я уже не могу с всё давай
money Hello  I'm in this To be honest, I
бабки Привет я в этом Если честно я в
don't understand much about this But
этом сильно не разбираюсь А вот вот тебе
why do you need me from a professional point of
зачем мне из профессиональной точки
view I'm telling you, I'm an architect Yes, but
зрения Я же говорю я архитектор Да а вот
why do I need to explain this to you Yes, look,
тебе зачем это надо объясняю Да смотри у
I have a scientific work So I have a scientific work,
меня научная работа Так я у меня научна
I have a scientific work so  architecture and
у меня научная работа так архитектура и
life of the Soviet Union of
быт Советского Союза
the seventies and eighties, so I
семидесятых-восьмидесятых годов вот я
see that your building was built somewhere in the
вижу что у вас построение как раз где-то
seventies and eighties, and I’m
семидесятых-восьмидесятых годов так и я
studying this too. That is, how they lived, yes, I’m
вот это изучаю То есть как жили да я
writing, I’m collecting material like that, no, you,
пишу я собираю материал такой нет вы вы
you would be better, you would  It would be better if you thought better about
вы бы лучше вы бы лучше вы бы лучше о
yourself, which one So we Look, I’m
себе подумали какую Так мы Смотри Я
studying no Look, I’m studying throughout the entire
изучаю нет Смотри Я изучаю на всей
territory of the Soviet Union, both in
территории Советского Союза как в
Ukraine and in Kazakhstan Everything I
Украине как в Казахстане Всё я с всюду
was fine with everywhere, but in Russia, like,
нормально было а в России типа на вёдра
they went to buckets Well, how the hell did they
ходили Ну как это блин на ведро и
come up with a bucket?  with a lid because so
придумали ведро с крышкой потому что
that you can
чтобы можно
call it a septic tank, okay, I ran because I still have to
назвать ладно побежал потому что надо
finish writing the scientific work, there is
ещё дописывать научную работу уже време
no letter on the Telegram right now and
нет пись на й Telegram прям зараз овин а
Popik is even more and more polite YouTube,
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
taking us through the skarg Orcs in your ban and I
заня нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и
don’t show too many videos  I
дуже багато видео не показую людям
don’t always show people information about ST for this purpose
вчасно не показу информация про СТ тому
so that we can write a Mali operational link
для того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
right away and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm vdeo the same tsikava and korisna
окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are guilty of you trimati
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
independantly in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine  writing
YouTube Слава украини пись